fiio.net 2017-06-08

# Fiio-Born for Music and Happy

FiiO respect and protect the personal privacy of all the users in using any network service on www.fiio.net. In order to provide you  
with more accurate and more personalized service, FiiO will use or disclose your personal information in accordance with provisions of 

this Privacy Policy and handle with high discretion. Except any other regulations of this Privacy Policy, FiiO will not disclose the information 

or provide to any third party without your prior permission. FiiO will update this Privacy Policy from time to time. This Privacy is an integral 

part of the service agreement of FiiO, so you are deemed to agree with this Private Policy when you agree with the service agreement of FiiO.

**1\. Scope of application**

a) Required personal information when registering account on FiiO official website.  
b) User information you provided in the FiiO account center when registering for product exchange or other activities that organized by FiiO.  
c) Other personal information that FiiO acquired through proper means. You are aware of and agree that the following information do not apply in this Privacy Policy: 

1) The key words in your published comments on FiiO forum.  
2) Your public information available on FiiO forum, including but not limited to, activity participation, transaction information, and other sharing information.  
3) Any behavior that goes against law or regulations of FiiO forum.

**2\. Use of information**

a) Without your prior permission, FiiO will not provide it to any third party, nor to sell, rent, share or do any transaction.  
b) FiiO will not allow any third party to collect, edit, sell or distribute your personal information free of charge.  
c) To provide better service to users, FiiO will provide you with possible information to your interests according to your personal information.

**3\. Disclosure of information**

In the following cases, FiiO will disclose your personal information fully or partially in accordance with your personal willingness or legal regulations:

a) Disclose it to the third party with your prior permission.  
b) To provide you with the requested products or services, FiiO have to share your personal information with the third party.  
c) In accordance with the relevant provisions of the law or other regulations of administrative or judicial organization, FiiO disclose it to the third party, administrative or judicial organization.  
d) In case of any violation to relevant law or regulations, rules of FiiO service agreement caused by your behavior, FiiO have  to disclose your personal information to the third party.  
e) If you are a qualified intellectual property owner and already filed a lawsuit, on the reasonable request of the accused person, FiiO have to disclose the information so as to settle the dispute.  
f) Other situations that FiiO deem as proper according to law, regulation or the policy of website.

**4\. Storage of information**

All your information and related data that acquired by FiiO will be stored on FiiO server or affiliated companies of FiiO.

**5\. Security of information**

a) There is security protection function for each FiiO account. And FiiO will use security precautions such as encrypted password to protect your information from any loss, 

abuse or alteration. Despite the security measures, you are still required to keep your username and password well, since there is no perfect security on network.  
b) When using FiiO network services, please properly protect your personal information, and only disclose to others when necessary. 

If you find your username and password of FiiO account has been disclosed, please contact FiiO immediately to take corresponding measures.
